Guide to the Paula Green papers, 1940-2013 and undated RL.11500
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Paula Green Advertising (PGA), 1969-2004 and undated; 5
  - Accounts--Sterling National Bank, 1971-1996 and undated; 23
    - Elephant cartoon, undated (Box 54)
    - Invoices, 1990-1992 (Box 54)
    - Letter to shareholders (Box 55)
    - Lou Cappelli speech, 1992-1993 (Box 55)
    - Media planning, 1994 (Box 55)
    - Mexico campaign (Spanish), 1995 (Box 55)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987-1990 (Box 69)
    - "Money in the Bank" campaign, 1990 (Box 55)
    - Newsletters, 1993-1995 (Box 55)
    - Press and printed material, 1988-1994 (Box 55)
    - Print advertising, campaigns, 1979-1994 and undated; 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Print advertising, campaigns, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Print advertising, campaigns, 1971 and undated; 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Progress report drafts, 1994 (Box 55)
    - Radio, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Report: How Sterling Can Make the Most of Its 50th Anniversary, 1978 (Box 55)
    - Spot radio schedules and invoices, 1990-1992 (Box 56)
    - Sterling Bank Services, undated (Box 56)
  - Accounts--Subaru Dealerships, 1981; 24
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 56)
  - New Business, 1969-1996 and undated; 25
    - Bongrain International (Alouette), 1989-1990 (Box 56)
    - Callaway Vineyard and Winery, 1979 (Box 56)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1979-1991; 4 folders (Box 56)
    - Corespondence--The Hon. John R. McKennan Jr. on Hathaway, 1996 (Box 56)
    - Cosmetics industry, 1977-1988; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Credentials file, undated (Box 57)
    - The Custom Shop, 1984-1985 (Box 57)
    - Digital Equipment Corporation, 1978-1984 (Box 57)
    - Food industry, 1977-1982; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Good Housekeeping, 1990 (Box 58)
    - House and Garden, 1981 (Box 58)
    - IBM, 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - National Geographic, 1982 (Box 58)
    - New York Health and Fitness, 1986-1992 (Box 58)
    - Pasta & Cheese, 1985 (Box 58)
    - Paul's Restaurant, 1987 (Box 58)
    - Perma Ceram, 1982 (Box 58)
    - Prospect file, undated (Box 58)
    - Revlon, 1969-1986; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Rubigo Cosmetics, 1981 (Box 58)
    - Scott Paper, 1982 (Box 58)
    - Tsing-Tao Beer, 1980 (Box 58)
    - Unions, 1979-1980 (Box 58)
    - Wendy's, undated (Box 58)
    - Wine industry, 1980-1981 (Box 58)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1959-2013 and undated; 6
  - 1. Paramount Chickens, 1976 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-001)
    Master Cassette: Success Story :30; Leftovers :30; Mama Hen :30; Tag :30; Pots :30. Nat B. Eisenberg and Associates.
  - 3. Paramount Chickens, 1976 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-002)
    Busy Takes: Success Story :30; Leftovers :30; Mama Hen :30; Tag :30; Pots :30. Nat B. Eisenberg and Associates.
  - 4. Paramount Chickens, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-003)
    Pearlie's Chickens :60; Mama's Kitchen :30; Washing :60; 6 Chickens :30; Stuffing :30
  - 5. Paramount Chickens, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-004)
    Washing :60; 6 Chickens :30; Stuffing :30
  - 8. Paramount Chickens, 1974 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-005)
    All Dressed Up; Full Line; Show and Tell; Telephone No.; Protein
  - 9. Paramount Chickens, 1976 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-006)
    Tag; Alt. :30
  - 10. Paramount Chickens, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-007)
    Chicken Story; Segment; Color; Kosher, Pearl.
  - 11. Paramount Chickens, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-008)
    Pearl's Kitchen; show promo for book
  - 12. Paramount Chickens, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-009)
    Recipe Book spot with Pearl
  - 202. ILGWU, 1990 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-010)
    Lillian, Working Mother :60
  - 218. ILGWU, 1976 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-011)
    Barbees; Bledsoes
  - 224. ILGWU, 1976 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-012)
    Original Material. Lillian; Emma; Generations
  - 232. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-013)
    Imports; Prine II
  - 244. ILGWU, 1977 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-014)
    Blouses; outdoor and indoor :60
  - 255. ILGWU, 1977 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-015)
    Lydia: Blouses with indoor chorus :60
  - 261. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-016)
    Bledsoes; Blouses/Meredith with outdoor chorus; Jim Prine/Imports with indoor chorus
  - 268. ILGWU, 1978 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-017)
    Norma II; indoor and outdoor choruses
  - 305. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-018)
    The Bledsoes with chorus III :60 finished spot
  - 306. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-019)
    The Bledsoes with chorus III :60 with (Saul) Charkin
  - 310. Sixty Minutes (CBS), 1979 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-020)
    Segment on undocumented aliens
  - 312. ILGWU, 1988 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-021)
    Georgia spot
  - 312. ILGWU, 1982 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-022)
    Georgia :60 with full chorus
  - 312. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-023)
    Georgia to CBS News
  - 319. ILGWU, 1980 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-024)
    Chorus 3 with and without C :40
  - 330. ILGWU, 1980 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-025)
    Work picture of report to convention
  - 332. ILGWU, 1980 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-026)
    Report to convention finished tape 26:00
  - 332. ILGWU, 1980 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-027)
  - 333. Tonight Show (WNBC TV), Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-028)
    Mention of ILGWU
  - 334. ILGWU, 1980 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-029)
    Convention news coverage
  - 335. Tonight Show (WNBC TV), Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-030)
    Review of new shows
  - 336. Carol Jenkins WNBC TV News, 1980 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-031)
    Talks about opening of ILGWU convention
  - 338. Tonight Show (WNBC TV), Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-032)
    Johnny Carson joking about ILGWU
  - 339. Archie Bunker's Place, Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-033)
    Wildcat Strike episode
  - 340. WNBC, WPIX, Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-034)
    President Carter in New York
  - 343. Mandrell Show, 1981 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-035)
    Skit between Barbara and her sister. One of the sisters sings first line of "look for the union label" song
  - 344. Bosom Buddies (WABC TV), Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-036)
    ILGWU mention
  - 345. Independent News WPIX, 1981 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-037)
  - 349. WCBS TV, Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-038)
    A Look Back at the Labor Day Parade
  - 351. So Fine (film), 1981 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-039)
    Reel 2; tape to tape 710-893
  - 355. The Facts of Life (WNBC TV), Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-040)
    Look for the Union Label
  - 356. The Dukes of Hazzard, 1982 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-041)
    Union Label--Dukes of Hazzard
  - 357. Filthy Rich (CBS TV), 1982 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-042)
    Union Label remark
  - 359. NFL Sports, Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-043)
    Player strike, union label song
  - 365. ILGWU, 1983 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-044)
    Americans Helping Americans/Beverly :30
  - 365A. ILGWU, 1983 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-045)
    Clothes in Your Closet/Joan :30
  - 367. Tonight (WNBC TV), Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-046)
    Abraham Lincoln skit, Look for the Union Label
  - 369. Gloria (WCBS), Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-047)
    ILGWU song
  - 370. WNBC TV, NBC NET, Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-048)
    Cool Whip and the Union Label Ladies
  - 371. Tonight Show (WNBC TV), Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-049)
    Johnny Carson singing the ILGWU song
  - 372. Show introductions, Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-050)
    This Week with David Brinkley; Good Morning America; Today; Nightline
  - 375. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-051)
    Circle Line Scene plus intro; "Paternity"
  - 378. Walter Mondale, Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-052)
    Dub of Mondale and the Labor vote
  - 380. ILGWU, 1984 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-053)
    Reel 2: takes 88-186
  - 380. ILGWU, 1984 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-054)
    Reel 1
  - 381. ILGWU, 1985 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-055)
    Voting :30
  - 381. ILGWU, 1985 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-056)
  - 381. ILGWU, 1985 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-057)
  - 383. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-058)
    Union series; one segment uses "Union Label" women's story
  - 384. ABC News, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-059)
    Made in the USA
  - 385. The Willmar 8, 1985 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-060)
  - 386. Nightly News (WNBS TV), Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-061)
    CWA union story
  - 387. Today in New York (WNBC TV), Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-062)
    Saul Charkin, President of ILGWU
  - 389. ILGWU, 1979 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-063)
    Georgia chorus III :60
  - 390A. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-064)
    Reel 1 with time code
  - 390B. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-065)
    Reel 2 with time code
  - 391. ILGWU, 1987 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-066)
    Statue rev. :30
  - 391A. ILGWU, 1986 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-067)
    Statue for air, not for air, two spots :30
  - 392. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-068)
    Statue of Liberty footage
  - 394. Nightly Business Report, 1986 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-069)
  - 395. Fame, 1985 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-070)
    Broadway Danny Amatullo final master copy
  - 396. Labor Day, Erie Pa., 1982 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-071)
  - 397. Watch on Washington, 1987 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-072)
    Segment on textiles and trade 11:45
  - 400. Standard Milling Co. (Wheatena), Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-073)
    Janie :30; Rosalyn :30; Alan :30; Darren :30
  - 401. Standard Milling Co. (Wheatena), 1974 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-074)
    Darren :30
  - 401: ILGWU, 1983 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-075)
    Americans Helping Americans/Beverly :30; Clothes in Your Closet/Kathy :30; Clothes in Your Closet/Joan :30
  - 402. Hecker's Flour, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-076)
    Take 77: Isabelle
  - 406. Hecker's Flour/Ceresota Flour, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-077)
    Isabelle :30
  - 412. Hecker's Flour, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-078)
  - 425. ILGWU, 1988 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-079)
    Multi-shop: Join In :30
  - 425. ILGWU, 1988 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-080)
  - 426. ILGWU, 1988 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-081)
    Production Material Reel 2 60:00
  - 426. ILGWU, 1988 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-082)
    Production Material Reel 3 60:00
  - 426. ILGWU, 1988 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-083)
    Production Material Reel 1 60:00
  - 426A. ILGWU, 1988 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-084)
    Multi-shop soundtrack only
  - 427. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-085)
    Japan master edit
  - 428A. Free to Be (WABC TV), Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-086)
    ILGWU
  - 428B. Free to Be (WABC TV), Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-087)
  - 428C. Free to Be: A Family, 1988 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-088)
    Marlo Thomas and Friends no commercial slugs
  - 429. ILGWU, 1989 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-089)
    Report to convention I; protection master not used
  - 430. Warwick Advertising, 1989 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-090)
    Crafted with Pride/Made in the USA: Department Store rev. :30; Quick Changes--Spring Summer :30
  - 432. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-091)
    Multi-shop Join In :30; Lillian :30; Statue :30; Song We Sing :30
  - 433. A Current Affair, 1990 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-092)
  - 434. ILGWU, 1990 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-093)
    On Stage :30
  - 435. ILGWU, 1990 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-094)
  - 437. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-095)
    Susan :30; Judy and Jasmine :30; Ramona :30
  - 437. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-096)
  - 438A. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-097)
    Reel 1 and 2: Group shots and singles of group members
  - 438B. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-098)
    Reel 3: Singles and group men, three-somes, two shots
  - 438C. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-099)
    Tape 4: Banner; Susan Ransom
  - 438D. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-100)
    Tape 5 30:00
  - 438E. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-101)
    Tape 6 30:00
  - 438F. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-102)
    Tape 7: Ramona and Julio; Art card; Nat and Paula 30:00
  - 439. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-103)
    Casting session for vignettes
  - 440. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-104)
    Georgia; Jim Prine; Meredith; Voting; Statue; Susan; Judy; Ramona
  - 442. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-105)
    On Stage II :30
  - 442. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-106)
    On State II :30
  - 442B. ILGWU, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-107)
  - 443. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-108)
    Union Label Committee presentation
  - 444. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-109)
    Convention presentation to Union Label Seminar
  - 446A. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-110)
    Joel and Perry's Excellent Shoot; Roxanne reel 1 handheld factory/TV production
  - 446B. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-111)
    Joel and Perry's Excellent Shoot; Roxanne reel 2 handheld factory
  - 446C. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-112)
    Joel and Perry's Excellent Shoot; Roxanne reel 3 handheld factory
  - 447A. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-113)
    Wild footage shot in Neptune, N.J. at Roxanne factory, Reel 1, part 1 of 2
  - 447B. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-114)
    Wild footage shot in Neptune, N.J. at Roxanne factory, Reel 2, part 1 of 2
  - 448. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-115)
    Alan Green's Roxanne factory shoot "auditions"
  - 448A. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-116)
    Factory shoot Roxanne
  - 449. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-117)
    We Make Jobs :30
  - 450. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-118)
  - 450. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-119)
  - 451. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-120)
  - 451. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-121)
  - 451. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-122)
  - 452. ILGWU, 1988-1991 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-123)
    Banners
  - 453. ILGWU, 1988-1991 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-124)
  - 454A. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-125)
    Roughcut A roll (people talking)
  - 454B. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-126)
    Roughcut B roll (people working, dolly shots)
  - 454C. ILGWU, Undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-127)
    Roughcut B roll #2 (bathing suit shots and labels being sewn)
  - 455. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-128)
  - 456. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-129)
  - 456A. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-130)
    Report to Convention audio tracks
  - 456B. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-131)
    Mini doc for Convention 92 Roxanne factory and auditions; rough cut no narration
  - 456D. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-132)
    Convention report materials, graphic only
  - 457. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-133)
    Union Label Committee titles
  - 458. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-134)
    Pt. 1 Lillian, Working Mother; Pt. 2 Union Label Seminar
  - 459. ILGWU, 1992 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-135)
    8 representative commercials, 1976-1991; 1-5 union vs. imports 1976-1986; 6-8 union and families 1991
  - 462A. ILGWU, 1994 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-136)
    Casting tape 1
  - 462B. ILGWU, 1994 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-137)
    Casting tape 2
  - 465(I). ILGWU, 1994 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-138)
    Health Care :30
  - 465(II). ILGWU, 1994 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-139)
  - 600. American Cancer Society, Undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-140)
    Buddy Hackett promo
  - 601. Green Dolmatch demo reel, 1973 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-141)
    Lee's Carpets; Galey and Lord; SOS Soap Pads; Soggy Cereal; Life Cereal
  - 602. News Center 4, 1975 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-142)
    Betty Furness remarks on Maypo
  - 603. Dinah Shore: Dinah's Place, 1972 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-143)
    Helen Hayes
  - 604. Ann Medina/Breast Cancer, Undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-144)
  - 605. Green Dolmatch anniversary party, Undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-145)
  - 606. American Cancer Society, Undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-146)
    Paula Green on Action 9 program
  - 607. U.S. Public Health Service program "You" about smoking problems, Undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-147)
  - 609. U.S. Public Health Service, Undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-148)
    You've Come a Long Way, Baby :60; Zora Lampert :20; Still :30
  - 610. Subaru, Undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-149)
    Uphill :30; Snow Storm :60; Soccer Balls :30
  - 611. Green Dolmatch anniversary party, Undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-150)
  - 612. Straight Talk, Undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-151)
  - 613. U. S. Public Health Service, 1973 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-152)
    Woman and Smoking; Stills; Good Reasons
  - 614. New York Times Experiment, 1975 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-153)
    Bob Levinson camera test
  - 616. Show reel, Undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-154)
    New York Times 8 commercials; Subaru 3 commercials; Paramount Poultry 5 commercials
  - 616. Show reel, Undated (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-155)
  - 615. Harry O (TV series): Anatomy of a Frame, 1975 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-156)
  - 617. American Cancer Society, Undated (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-157)
    Lola Falana 8 commercials
  - 619. Jeanne Parr Show, Undated (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-158)
  - 620. Straight Talk with Paula Green, George Lois, Frankie Cadwell, Undated (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-159)
    How Advertising Portrays Women
  - 621. U.S. Public Health Service, 1982 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-160)
    Stanley auditions; Nicky Counselman, Nancy Lester, Georgia Creighton, Joan See
  - 621. American Cancer Society Smoking Clinic, 1977 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-161)
  - 622. American Cancer Society, 1977 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-162)
    Great American Smokeout
  - 623. American Cancer Society, 1979 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-163)
    Smokewatch :10 and :30
  - 633. Second Careers Volunteer Program, 1980 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-164)
    Second Careers People; People B
  - 633. Second Careers Volunteer Program, 1980 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-165)
    Second Careers People :30 and :10
  - 633. Second Careers Volunteer Program, 1980 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-166)
  - 635. Show reel, 1981 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-167)
    Burlington: Lee's Carpets; USPHS Stills; American Cancer Society: Breast Exam, PAP test; Burlington: Galey and Lord
  - 636. Beechnut Life Savers, 1981 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-168)
    Remembering film transfer
  - 637. Show reel, Undated (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-169)
    New York Times; Subaru; Paramount Poultry; Goya Foods; Marval Poultry; Standard Milling; Sterling National Bank; American Cancer Society; ILGWU
  - 637. Show reel, 1982 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-170)
  - 638. The Reel Paula Green, 1981 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-171)
  - 639. The Reel Paula Green, Undated (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-172)
  - 640. Subaru, 1981 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-173)
    Because :30; Soccer Balls :30; Snow Storm :60
  - 641. The Reel Paula Green, Undated (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-174)
  - 642. Roberta Silbert at Friar's Roast of Buddy Hackett, 1981 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-175)
  - 643. Dow Chemical :30, Undated (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-176)
  - 643. U.S. Public Health Service, 1983 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-177)
    Cigarette World :60
  - 644. Revlon presentation, 1987 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-178)
  - 645. Food for Thought special presentation, 1989 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-179)
  - 646. Casera presentation, 1989 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-180)
  - 648. WLR Foods presentation, 1990 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-181)
  - 700. New York Times, Undated (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-182)
    Bradley; Cross; Kelly
  - 701. New York Times, Undated (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-183)
    Conductor and tuba takes
  - 702. New York Times, Undated (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-184)
    Home Delivery :10; Tuba player, organist
  - 703. New York Times, Undated (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-185)
    Whirling Ball--John Horsey :30
  - 704. New York Times, 1975 (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-186)
    Classified Section :10
  - 705. New York Times, 1975 (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-187)
  - 706. New York Times, 1973 (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-188)
  - 707. New York Times, Undated (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-189)
  - 709. New York Times, 1973 (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-190)
    Ted; Joan; Business
  - 710; New York Times, Undated (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-191)
    Ted; Joan :10
  - 711. New York Times, 1975 (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-192)
    Arts and Leisure/Bacall selected takes
  - 712. New York Times, Undated (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-193)
    Buddy Hackett :30
  - 713. New York Times, 1975 (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-194)
    Best Foods Day
  - 714. New York Times, Undated (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-195)
    Organist, tuba takes
  - 717. New York Times, Undated (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-196)
    Robert Loggia; Tammy Grimes; Kevin Conway; Belilnda Cusak
  - 718. New York Times, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-197)
    Buddy Hackett all takes
  - 719. New York Times, 1976 (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-198)
    Doctors :30
  - 720. New York Times, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-199)